(THIS SERIES IS AN ADULT ANIMATION
INTENDED FOR VIEWERS WHO ARE OF LEGAL AGE
ACCORDING TO LOCAL LAWS AND REGULATIONS.)
(THIS STORY IS PURELY FICTIONAL AND BEARS
NO RELATION TO REAL PEOPLE, ORGANIZATIONS, OR EVENTS.)
(ALL CHARACTERS ARE OF LEGAL AGE OF CONSENT.)
(THE TITLE MAY CONTAIN SENSITIVE CONTENT
SUCH AS SEXUAL OR VIOLENT SCENES. DO NOT IMITATE.)
ALL CHARACTERS, ORGANIZATIONS, PLACES,
We are the Anti-Copulation Force.
LAWS AND NAMES ARE PURELY FICTIONAL.
We bring down the hammer of justice...
PLEASE BE AWARE THAT THE WORK
on all loveless, perverted sex.
CONTAINS SOME EXTREME LANGUAGE.
The Anti-Copulation...
Force?
NUKITASHI THE ANIMATION
Just the failed creations
of the ones before
Some rebel elements, rotten to the core
Beyond the wire fence,
a world of sleek design
I stared it down,
a secret that was only mine
Inside the perfect world
that someone else designed
If we were different,
we were always left behind
In a gentle world for everyone to behold
Someone untold cried in agony
Just a laughing mob,
a mindless flock of crows,
Always saying "NO"
to things that nobody knows
With values and with normalcy they pose
Armed with all their theories, I suppose
And then they call us useless pros
Even if you know
that you are in the wrong
Remember what it means
to live your life and to be strong
If you truly wish
you could change today right now
With that very heart,
go on and show them
Don't you hesitate, don't ever stop
Destroy it, make the whole world drop
With all that passion,
pierce right through it all
Go anywhere you want
Can't even love yourself?
For the impatience or the mess you've made
Because right here and now,
we're standing tall
We are alive and breathing after all
Rin-san, isn't that person Nanase Katagiri?
What? The Legendary XXX?
No way.
That's a non-sexer.
You bastard! Laying a hand on a loli
is strictly forbidden.
You know that, don't you?
You are wrong.
Takeshi is only four.
We were having
platonic sex between a shota and a loli.
Ugh...
Is this the darkside of modern society?
I'm not a loli, though.
Nanase, this loli is in a state
of shock and confusion.
Got it.
It's okay now.
That was scary, wasn't it?
There, there.
Heh?
Want some candy?
Oh, strawberry flavor! Yay!
But I'm not a loli!
Oh, that's right.
Here, look.
HINAMI WATARAI
Ta-da!
NOVEMBER 13
A student ID?
YEAR 3 CLASS 1 - BLOOD TYPE O
Oh, you have an older sister?
No, the photo is me, right?
Huh? It's you?
Which means...
That's right. I'm a perfectly respectable adult.
Ahem.
Then there's no problem
with having sex with you.
Huh?
If you're not a loli,
a little bit of aggressive lewdness is acceptable.
A girl that looks like a loli
and a kindergartener-uncle?
Or uncle-kindergartener?
Hey Rin-san, which is it?
It doesn't matter which!
More importantly...
what is this Anti-Copulation Force?
These guys are caught in the act of...
assaulting a four years old
and obstructing lewd sex.
Hurry up and catch them.
Alright, starting with you,
who will definitely...
lay hands on a real loli someday!
Ow ow ow! No I'm not.
Takeshi's not at fault!
Dammit!
This is a pain,
so I'm hauling you all in.
Jun, what should we do?
We're getting out of here.
Ah.
W-Wait.
W-Wait for me!
Hold still!
Would it be bad if we let them get away?
Huh?
Worse than bad!
It's a guaranteed demotion
and a major chewing out!
Mi is Mi in Misaki.
Sa is Sa in Misaki.
Ki is Ki in Misakiiiii.
You there!
Huh?
Stop! Non-sexer!
What could it be?
It's noisy over there.
I'm a little curious.
Heave-ho!
Halt!
This way!
Wait for me!
This is Squad 2, Rin Hanamaru.
We've confirmed the existence
of the Anti-Copulation Force.
After capture, we will proceed
to lewd sex for re-education.
Please send the target's location data.
We will maintain the wetness of the vagina
and restrain them with a warning shot.
Whoa, a pistol?
Didn't you say a warning shot?
Oh, right.
Ariadne Protocol, activate.
Asa-chan, wake up.
Prepare for electronic warfare!
Roger.
Unidentified vessel approaching!
Two bogeys,
approach in approximately five seconds.
Enemy wetness level is
gushing and overflowing.
Insertion possible with no foreplay!
Activating ECM.
Executing electronic countermeasures.
Noise jamming.
Commencing electronic interference.
My comms is...
Huh?
I can't hear anything.
D-Did you do something?
It's jamming.
LOOKS LIKE THEY LOST SIGHT OF THEM.
We are constantly...
transmitting our location data
through the SHO app.
So conversely, we can use the app's data...
to escape while performing
jamming countermeasures.
By combining the app data with information...
thermographic cameras installed
all over the island for STD checks,
the system analyzes everything from their gears,
wetness level and angle of erection,
to determine escape routes
and carry out countermeasures.
Can't find them anywhere.
Tch.
That is the Ariadne Protocol.
Changing route. Pattern 5.
Wait, big bro!
My processing can't keep up!
Hi.
I've found the naughty children.
The system was a bit impotent,
so it was quite a struggle to find you.
Surrender and present your XXX and XXX.
If you resist, this thing will squirt.
Two bandits, both in a great flood state.
Insertion possible without kissing.
No choice. Let's do it.
Right.
Eh? Huh?
Switching radar to Dogfight Mode.
Master Arm, on.
Let's go! Engage!
Create a smokescreen, Nanase.
Throw Egg at 11 o'clock.
It's Pattern B.
Got it.
Eh? Huh?
Me too?
How impudent...
My cute little boy.
It's a smokescreen
created with smoke agents...
using steam and carbon dioxide gas.
An erection at 10 o'clock!
Found you!
Let out your precum!
Dummy Balloons?
These are my precious,
repeatedly improved air wives.
Where are you?
Such things...
Miyuki! Yoshi! Angelina!
That's what you get for naming them.
You can't escape.
Freeze.
Our demotion is on the line, you know.
Tsk, how persistent!
Hold on to me.
H-Huh?
- Huh?
- Rubber?
S-So cool! Like a ninja!
These are condoms modified by Jun.
With a special adhesive liquid
instead of lotion,
they can stick to anything
for a few seconds.
Are you okay?
First, a greeting.
But she kinda looks like
Nanase Katagiri, doesn't she?
The Legendary XXX?
There's no way that girl is a non-sexer.
Yeah, you're right.
Such a good little walker.
My little baby.
Now, put both hands behind your head...
swiftly bring your dick to full erection.
I have no weapon.
Not one for escaping, but for winning.
- Ah!
- Huh?
Huh?
What?
Where did that come from?
What is that?
F-From that distance? Impossible.
That is...
Jun.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Hold it right there, you craven cocks!
Surrender yourself to my XXX!
Next up is yellow!
Now's our chance!
So bright!
My eyes! My ears! My vagina!
It's a flashbang using
a fuse and aluminum particles.
Don't underestimate us.
To meet a wide range of needs,
FS has also mastered blindfolded play.
This white, thick liquid is...
A tearjerker containing polybutene
and a dioxide inhibitor.
Nice sacrifice, Noroman-san!
Let me take the credit somehow!
Last one is green!
S-Slippery goo?
That's just regular lotion.
This humiliation... I won't forgive you!
Anti-Copulation Force.
STUDENT COUNCIL ROOM
Ikuko, what were you doing?
It couldn't be helped.
The chain of command
wasn't functioning due to the jamming.
You were slacking off
with your radio turned off, weren't you?
It couldn't be helped!
My XXX was searching for a XXX!
No problem then.
But, Touka-sama...
An entity of higher priority than the
Anti-Copulation Force has now appeared.
Must be around here.
Find her at all costs!
She's with the Anti-Copulation Force!
Any response from XXX dowsing?
No radar contact.
Confirmed loss of enemy signal.
Looks like we managed to shake them.
Yeah, but Jun...
That sniper that saved us earlier,
could it be...
Yeah, no doubt about it.
To the warriors,
here are my instructions...
The mission given to us
by the mysterious person is...
The order handed down to us from SHO is...
Found her?
Not yet.
She should be around here.
What could it be?
A lot of FS members have gathered.
Eh?
Capture Fumino Kotoyose.
Heh!?
Who are you?
She is the only key to crushing
the Perverted Ordinance.
Who the hell are you?
Nukitashi.
I see.
I understand your situation now.
So, what's your name?
I'm Hinami Watarai.
Ah.
Thank you for saving me earlier.
Even though you've reached adulthood,
you were avoiding sex.
Naturally, you will join our organization, right?
Eh?
But it's not that I absolutely
didn't want to do anything lewd...
W-What did you say?
Are you an enemy?
Isn't it foolish to immediately judge
everyone as friend or foe?
However, if you're not on the side
of the Anti-Copulation Force,
why haven't you engaged in any lewd acts?
Um, that's because...
no one ever asked me to have sex.
You see, I have small boobs.
And my face is ugly.
So everyone didn't want to
have sex with me.
That's probably...
because you look exactly like a loli.
Huh?
On this island,
it's decided by the ordinance that...
you absolutely
cannot have sex with an underage child.
B-But what about the students at school?
They know I'm in the same grade, right?
Maybe it's because
if they have sex with you,
they'd be suspected of
eventually laying hands on a real loli?
I-It's true that I'm short and my boobs
are flat as a board,
but do I look like a child that much?
It's not that you're "like" one...
you are more of...
an absolutely pure loli.
I'm a loli?
No one has sex with me
because I'm a loli?
Gawh...
Kinda feel bad for her.
But this patheticness
is perfect for our team, isn't it?
Indeed, you should join our team.
But this is an organization
against the ordinance, right?
I can't cooperate with bad kids.
Hey, think about it carefully.
Shouldn't your first time...
be a wonderful experience
with someone you love?
Yeah, you're right.
I want my first time
to be with someone I like.
Hmm...
Anyway, what class are you in, Hinami-chan?
Eh? Ah, I'm in Class 1.
Third Year, Class 1.
- Huh?
- Heh?
Third year?
Then aren't you our senpai?
That's right.
Ahem.
Then, think of it as helping your juniors,
could you please join our team, senpai?
Senpai... Senpai... Senpai...
Senpai?
Ehehe.
It can't be helped.
I can't refuse a request from my juniors.
Ehehe.
How should I put this...
She's really...
a child.
Ehehe.
You can leave everything to your senpai.
Hey, that's him.
Seriously?
That average-looking guy with glasses?
Could it be that my identity was exposed?
Don't worry.
Your face was hidden by goggles.
And I'm the Legendary XXX.
To think he was screwing
that Katagiri over and over.
I want to screw her too.
I'm so jealous!
See, stand tall and proud.
But I feel like we're being targeted
for a different reason.
Apparently, he made the bitch XXX
orgasm over and over,
and caused a rain of XXX.
Was that yesterday's evening shower?
I want to be pierced by a XXX umbrella too.
I want to make XXX rain, too.
Not a rain dance but a squirt dance, right?
I should probably think of
other camouflage methods.
Hinami.
Heh?
R-Rei-chan.
Good morning.
Are you okay?
I heard a small child
was attacked by a perverted baby-man.
I-Is that so?
As you can see, I'm perfectly fine.
That's good then.
That's right. I heard that the girl
was just pretending to be an adult,
but was actually a pre-adult child.
Hmm?
But be careful.
Lately, a group of deviants
who interfere with lewd sex has appeared.
I-Is that so?
Yesterday's commotion on the back mountain
was caused by them.
They're called the Anti-Copulation Force.
The Anti-Copulation Force?
The commotion on the back mountain?
Luckily, eyewitness reports are coming in.
We'll capture them
and put them to the guillotine.
Could that girl also be...
Thank you very much
for your generous hospitality.
I will surely repay this kindness someday.
I-I haven't really done all that much.
More importantly,
are you perhaps part
of that Anti-Copulation Force?
If I had to say...
I knew it.
For such a polite and good child,
putting to guillotine is just too cruel.
Are you also a member
of the Anti-Copulation Force?
Huh?
From what I can see,
you haven't engaged in any lewd acts.
So I was part of the Anti-Copulation Force?
Hmm, Fumino Kotoyose... Fumino Kotoyose...
Hmm, there's no data anywhere.
But there's no doubt she exists.
I definitely saw her.
But I've already checked all resident data
and security camera footage.
At this rate, my fingers
are going to break from tendonitis.
I won't be able to do my daily routine
of arguing anonymously with idiots online.
If Fumino Kotoyose is the key
to crushing the Perverted Ordinance,
isn't it possible that FS
is also after her?
That's it, Nanase-chan!
I will hack into the FS data right away!
No good, it's locked.
How about infiltrating the FS
upper management's student council room...
and planting a backdoor on their PC?
Hmm, if we do that,
we might be able to extract information
without being noticed.
But is there an opportunity?
There is.
Minotsuki Academy's annual,
super-popular event.
We will now begin the school-wide assembly.
Students not yet in the gymnasium
are to stop having sex
and promptly resume in the gymnasium.
Wrong Size.
Low Hardness.
Insufficient Girth.
Ahh, it's so hard to find
a dick of destiny.
Is my dick really that bad?
They say a dick isn't just about its looks
That's right.
Look, your dick is... cheerful.
Even dick-judging?
Just you wait, someday
I'll bring down the hammer on you.
Don't you have a partner?
Wanna do it with me?
Look, a chastity belt.
So the rumors were true.
They say Nanase Katagiri
sucked all his semen dry.
And he's in that state until he recovers.
Impotent dick, a hopeless case.
Alright, I can avoid lewd sex
for a while with this.
That girl...
What's wrong, big bro?
Ah, there's a girl over there who's
unusually not having sex.
You're right.
Was there a girl like that in our school?
Ahh, her boobs are so big.
Die, big tits!
Don't say that, Wata-chan.
Loli shouldn't say things like "die".
I'm not a loli, and who's Wata-chan?
It's true, you seem more like
a "Wata-chan" than a "Hinami-chan."
Huh?
But I'm your senpai.
If there's data
on the Anti-Copulation Force within FS...
for that girl's sake,
and for my belly's sake,
I have to falsify FS's records.
That's forgery of official documents.
Good morning, everyone.
I am the student council president,
Touka Reizeiin.
President! Student Council Presideeent!
Touka-samaaaa!
As beautiful as eveeer!
You seem to be enjoying sex
from the bottom of your hearts.
That is excellent.
By engaging in lewd sex,
you can better understand your partner.
That is what I believe.
Who the hell is that?
That girl is in the same class as me.
She's a first-year?
Lewd sex
is a connection with another person.
A connection is, in other words, understanding.
Understanding is the very essence
of a pure human relationship.
What nonsense!
Did she just look this way?
Was it my imagination?
I need to focus on the mission.
To become a part
of your wonderful connections,
we will be holding
our annual event again this year.
That's right, the Sport-gasm Festival.
SURPRISE EJACULATION
THE SPORT-GASM FESTIVAL
Hey, it has been a while
We finally met again
I wonder, have you been doing okay
Just kidding! So happy,
but I'm also blushing
Hey, maybe not this one
maybe not that one too
I fret about the little things I've done
Will you even notice
I tried my very best
to dress up nicely for everyone
Should I be bold and make a move
No guarantee that you will approve
It's all or nothing? I can't do that
Ahhh, I think I have fallen flat
This story that I share with you
Has way too many options
Got to make my mind up and be brave
So the role of heroine is mine to be
It has to be real love
It must be from your love
Cause even I am so in love with you
A cliché story's not the thing for me
And laying plot points, how can that be
Worry, worry, worry, and then fall
Keep worrying and falling
It has to be real love
It must be from your love
Don't forget the promise that we made
I'm just kidding, a sweet lie is okay
Actually, what I want is the real thing
Ahhh... I'm begging, please love me